Me and my friend had an idea one day to
try the food from every country in the
world only in New York City. Every week
we're going to spin a wheel, land on a
random country,
>> Armenia. All right.
>> And then go find their food somewhere in
New York City. We decided on Little
Armenia Cafe in Greenpoint. So here's
our first stop on trying food from every
country in the world.
We met our good friend Arod here who's
chef owner and we said we wanted the
most authentic Armenian experience we
could have and he just said all right
>> guys the first thing I made for you is a
little tibuli salad traditional
Armenian. This is my mom's recipe.
Different Armenians make it different
ways. We're going to start with the
kush. This is a sparkling brute from
Armenia. As my purveyor said just think
of the juice and berries and
>> Oh yeah.
>> It was very good. Do you come from
Armenia? My parents are military
members, but they came from Iraq, you
know, because they were gen My
grandparents were genocide kids. So,
running from the genocide, you know,
Syria, Lebanon,
3,000 kids, you know.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Speaker check.
>> All right, we've got a little Armenian
soup. He said it was the Armenian
version of grilled cheese and tomato
soup.
>> That's broccoli red. Would you call
that? That's a secret right there.
>> All right. All right.
>> Now, we're two courses in, two glasses
of wine in, and we are feeling good.
We're feeling very Armenia right now,
actually.
>> See what's next.
>> It's amazing.
>> We're still waiting on you to have one,
too.
>> Yeah, it's coming.
>> It's coming.
>> How many could I eat?
>> Yeah.
>> 85.
>> It was just they didn't really put too
much love into it with these beautiful,
beautiful grapes. So, the documentary is
about as an American army.
>> Oh, wow. So, the wine we had was about
from the documentary. And this is our
Armenian plate. It's got mostly Armenian
stuff that people like. This is
>> very good, by the way. Dang. Five
glasses of wine in. Six dishes through
and we're feeling good.
>> It's getting emotional.
>> This is the point of the country. It's
like you're a part of this country.
You're a part of your own country. You
bring your culture here. People come.
They appreciate it. It's why we play.
>> This is why we play.
>> Crumble action.
>> Flipped upside cooked upside down.
Cooked upside down. Served right side
up.
>> That was dang.
>> That was absurd. That was one of the
best experiences of my life. Now to the
G train
times when I should ain't looking up.